usage: notebooklm-mcp-auth [-h] [--file [PATH]] [--port PORT] [--show-tokens]
                           [--no-auto-launch]

Authenticate with NotebookLM MCP

options:
  -h, --help        show this help message and exit
  --file [PATH]     Import cookies from file (recommended). Shows instructions
                    if no path given.
  --port PORT       Chrome DevTools port (default: 9222)
  --show-tokens     Show cached tokens (for debugging)
  --no-auto-launch  Don't automatically launch Chrome (requires Chrome to be
                    running with debugging)

This tool extracts authentication tokens from Chrome for use with the
NotebookLM MCP. TWO MODES: 1. FILE MODE (--file): Import cookies from a file
(RECOMMENDED) - Shows step-by-step instructions for extracting cookies -
Prompts you for the file path after you save the cookies - No Chrome remote
debugging required 2. AUTO MODE (default): Automatic extraction via Chrome
DevTools - Requires closing Chrome first - Launches Chrome and extracts
cookies automatically - May not work on all systems EXAMPLES: notebooklm-mcp-
auth --file # Guided file import (recommended) notebooklm-mcp-auth --file
~/cookies.txt # Direct file import notebooklm-mcp-auth # Auto mode (close
Chrome first) After authentication, start the MCP server with: notebooklm-mcp
